<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE U SYSTEM "U.dtd" >
<U>
<thing id="Various">
    <thing><p>Meditation is not a means to an end. It is both the means and the end.<br/>&#8212; Jiddu Krishnamurti</p></thing>
    <thing><p>Silence is not an absence but a presence.<br/>&#8212; Anne D. LeClaire</p></thing>
    <thing><p>If it weren't for my mind, my meditation would be excellent.<br/>&#8212; Ani Pema Chodron</p></thing>
    <thing><p>Peace comes from within. Do not seek it without.<br/>&#8212; Buddha</p></thing>
    <thing><p>You will not be punished for your anger, you will be punished by your anger.<br/>&#8212; Buddha</p></thing>
    <thing><p>We are nothing but interpenetrating spheres of being.<br/>&#8212; Anonymous</p></thing>
    <thing><p>Meditation must be continuous. The current of meditation must be present in all your activities.<br/>&#8212; Annamalai Swami</p></thing>
    <thing><p>Prayer is when you talk to God; meditation is when you listen to God.<br/>&#8212; Diana Robinson</p></thing>
    <thing><p>The affairs of the world will go on forever. Do not delay the practice of meditation.<br/>&#8212; Jetsun Milarepa</p></thing>
    <thing><p>Samsara is mind turned outwardly, lost in its projections. Nirvana is mind turned inwardly, recognizing its nature.<br/>&#8212; Tulku Urgyen Rinpoche</p></thing>
    <thing><p>Simply notice that you're aware. At any given moment, you can choose to follow the chain of thoughts, emotions, and sensations that reinforce a perception of yourself as vulnerable and limited, or to remember that your true nature is pure, unconditioned, and incapable of being harmed.<br/>&#8212; Yongey Mingyur Rinpoche</p></thing>
    <thing><p>Mere physical sitting is not enough. You have to sit carefully and attentively. Let your body and breathing sit. Let your mind and emotions sit. Let your blood circulation sit. Let everything sit. Then your sitting becomes indestructible, immovable.<br/>&#8212; Maezumi Roshi</p></thing>
    <thing><p>One hour of contemplation surpasses sixty years of worship.<br/>&#8212; Muhammad</p></thing>
    <thing><p>Loving-kindness towards ourselves doesn't mean getting rid of anything. It means we can still be crazy after all these years. We can still be angry after all these years. We can still be timid, jealous or full of feelings of unworthiness. The point is not to try to throw ourselves away and become something better. It's about befriending who we are already.<br/>&#8212; Pema Chodron</p></thing>
    <thing><p>Keep your heart clear and transparent and you will never be bound. A single disturbed thought creates ten thousand distractions.<br/>&#8212; Ryokan</p></thing>
    <thing><p>Meditation is a microcosm, a model, a mirror. The skills we practice when we sit are transferable to the rest of our lives.<br/>&#8212; Sharon Salzberg</p></thing>
    <thing><p>Meditation is the ultimate mobile device; you can use it anywhere, anytime, unobtrusively.<br/>&#8212; Sharon Salzberg</p></thing>
    <thing><p>All knowledge that the world has ever received comes from the mind; the infinite library of the universe is in our own mind.<br/>&#8212; Swami Vivekananda</p></thing>
    <thing><p>The secret of change is to focus all of your energy, not on fighting the old, but on building the new.<br/>&#8212; Socrates</p></thing>
    <thing><p>The true practice of meditation is to sit as if you were drinking water when you are thirsty.<br/>&#8212; Shunryu Suzuki</p></thing>
    <thing><p>Total relaxation is the secret to enjoying sitting meditation. I sit with my spine upright, but not rigid; and I relax all the muscles in my body.<br/>&#8212; Thich Nhat Hanh</p></thing>
    <thing><p>Meditation is the dissolution of thoughts in Eternal awareness or Pure consciousness without objectification, knowing without thinking, merging finitude in infinity.<br/>&#8212; Voltaire</p></thing>
    <thing><p>If you want others to be happy, practice compassion. If you want to be happy, practice compassion.<br/>&#8212; H.H. Dalai Lama</p></thing>
    <thing><p>Generally we waste our lives, distracted from our true selves, in endless activity. Meditation is the way to bring us back to ourselves, where we can really experience and taste our full being.<br/>&#8212; Sogyal Rinpoche</p></thing>
    <thing><p>All of man's difficulties are caused by his inability to sit, quietly, in a room by himself.<br/>&#8212; Blaise Pascal</p></thing>
    <thing><p>If your mind is empty, it is always ready for anything; it is open to everything. In the beginner's mind there are many possibilities, in the expert's mind there are few.<br/>&#8212; Shunryu Suzuki</p></thing>
</thing>


<ref name="text" src="//U/thing[@id='Various']"></ref>

</U>
