<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE U SYSTEM "U.dtd" >
<U>
<thing id="Various">
  <thing><p>Therefore all things whatsoever ye would that men should do to you: do ye even so to them: for this is the law and the prophets<br/>&#8212; Matthew 7:12</p></thing>
  <thing><p>Lord, make me an instrument of Your peace. Where there is hatred, let me sow love; where there is injury, pardon; where there is doubt, faith; where there is despair, hope; where there is darkness, light; where there is sadness, joy.<br/>&#8212; St. Francis</p></thing>
  <thing><p>Evil has no positive nature; but the loss of good has received the name &quot;evil&quot;.<br/>&#8212; St Augustine</p></thing>
  <thing><p>In the beginning was the Word, and the Word was with God, and the Word was God.<br/>&#8212; John 1:1</p></thing>
  <thing><p>There is no Jew or Greek, slave or free, male or female; for you are all one in Christ Jesus.<br/>&#8212; Galatians 3:28</p></thing>
  <thing><p>Make every effort to live in peace with everyone and to be holy; without holiness no one will see the Lord.<br/>&#8212; Hebrews 12:14</p></thing>
  <thing><p>His disciples asked him and said to him, &quot;Do you want us to fast? How should we pray? Should we give to charity? What diet should we observe?&quot; Jesus said, &quot;Don't lie, and don't do what you hate, because all things are disclosed before heaven. After all, there is nothing hidden that will not be revealed, and there is nothing covered up that will remain undisclosed&quot;. <br/>&#8212; Thomas 6</p></thing>
  <thing><p>Jesus said, &quot;I am the light that is over all things. I am all: from me all came forth, and to me all attained.  Split a piece of wood; I am there.  Lift up the stone, and you will find me there&quot;. <br/>&#8212; Thomas 77</p></thing>
  <thing><p>Human rights are not only violated by terrorism, repression or assassination, but also by unfair economic structures that creates huge inequalities.<br/>&#8212; Pope Francis</p></thing>
  <thing><p>It is not fitting, when one is in God's service, to have a gloomy face or a chilling look.<br/>&#8212; St Francis of Assisi</p></thing>
  <thing><p>Holy wisdom confounds Satan and all his wickednesses.<br/>&#8212; St Francis of Assisi</p></thing>
  <thing><p>The world is a book, and those who do not travel read only a page.<br/>&#8212; St Augustine</p></thing>
  <thing><p>O Lord, help me to be pure, but not yet.<br/>&#8212; St Augustine</p></thing>
  <thing><p>This world's a bubble.<br/>&#8212; St Augustine</p></thing>
  <thing><p>More tears are shed over answered prayers than unanswered ones.<br/>&#8212; St Teresaof Avila</p></thing>
  <thing><p>Christianity's goal is not escape from this world. It loves this world and seeks to change it for the better.<br/>&#8212; Marcus Borg</p></thing>
  <thing><p>Beauty saves. Beauty heals. Beauty motivates. Beauty unites. Beauty returns us to our origins, and here lies the ultimate act of saving, of healing, of overcoming dualism.<br/>&#8212; Matthew Fox</p></thing>
  <thing><p>Jesus called for nonviolent resistance to Rome and just distribution of land and food. He was crucified because he threatened Roman stability - not as a sacrifice to God for humanity's sins.<br/>&#8212; John Dominic Crossan</p></thing>
  <thing><p>Jesus is what God looks like in sandals.<br/>&#8212; John Dominic Crossan</p></thing>
  <thing><p>The most important hour is always the present.<br/>The most significant person is precisely the one sitting across from you right now.<br/>The most necessary work is always love..<br/>&#8212; Meister Eckhart</p></thing>
  <thing><p>There is a huge silence inside each of us that beckons us into itself, and the recovery of our own silence can begin to teach us the language of heaven.<br/>&#8212; Meister Eckhart</p></thing>
  <thing><p>Apprehend God in all things, for God is in all things. Every single creature is full of God and is a book about God. Every creature is a word of God.<br/>&#8212; Meister Eckhart</p></thing>
  <thing><p>When a man sees the one in all things, he is above mere understanding.<br/>&#8212; Meister Eckhart</p></thing>
</thing>

<ref name="text" src="//U/thing[@id='Various']"></ref>

</U>
