<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE U SYSTEM "U.dtd" >
<U>

  <thing><p>I disagree strongly with whoever this quote is attributed to.<br/>&#8212; Randall Munroe</p></thing>
  <thing><p>This quote was taken out of context.<br/>&#8212; Randall Munroe</p></thing>
  <thing><p>This quote is often falsely attributed to Mark Twain.<br/>&#8212; Randall Munroe</p></thing>
  <thing><p>I'm being quoted to introduce something, but I have no idea what it is and certainly don't endorse it.<br/>&#8212; Randall Munroe</p></thing>
  <thing><p>This quote is very memorable.<br/>&#8212; Randall Munroe</p></thing>
  <thing><p>I wrote this book, and the person quoting me here is taking credit for it.<br/>&#8212; Randall Munroe</p></thing>
  <thing><p>This entire thing is the quote, not just the part in the quote marks. [Quote marks, brackets, and editors's note are all in the original.<br/>&#8212; Randall Munroe</p></thing>
  <thing><p>Websites that collect quotes are full of mistakes and never check original sources.<br/>&#8212; Randall Munroe</p></thing>
  <thing><p>This quote will be the only part of this presentation that you remember.<br/>&#8212; Randall Munroe</p></thing>
  <thing><p>Oooh, look at me, I looked up a quote!<br/>&#8212; Randall Munroe</p></thing>
  <thing><p>If you are doing a text search in this document for the word 'Butts', the good news is that it's here, but the bad news is that it only appears in this unrelated quote.<br/>&#8212; Randall Munroe</p></thing>
  <thing><p>Wait, what if these quote marks are inside out, so everything in the rest of the document is the quotation and this part isn't? Duuuuuude.<br/>&#8212; Randall Munroe</p></thing>
  <thing><p>The editors of <i>Bartlett's Familiar Quotations</i> are a bunch of cowards who don't have the guts to print this.<br/>&#8212; Randall Munroe</p></thing>
  <thing><p>This quote only looks profound when it's in a script font over a sunset.<br/>&#8212; Randall Munroe</p></thing>
  <thing><p>I don't do a lot of public speaking, so I looked up a memorable quote to start my speech, and this is what I found.  OK, you're staring at me blankly, but this whole thing is a quote.  I know that sounds confusing, but... you know what, never mind.<br/>&#8212; Randall Munroe</p></thing>

  
  <ref name="text" src="//U[1]/thing"></ref>

</U>
